

PROFILE-

Having 4.4 years of experience in developing web-based applications using MVC.NET, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular and Entity Framework. Strong in Object Oriented Programming concepts. Flexibility and Adaptability in regards with new technologies and environments. Ability to work effectively with Global project teams. Excellent organizational ability in handling time critical and multi-tasking environment.

CONTACT

NIACI		
	+1 (816)-769-7186	
	murali.ofc@outlook.com	>

in.linkedin.com/in/muralichukka in

https://chkrish9.github.io/Portfolio

AWARDS-



Applause award (April 2018) – Deloitte (India).



Best coding award (September 2015) – HCL (India).

SKILLS———	
Client-side Technologies:	
HTML 5	
CSS 3	
SASS	
BOOTSTRAP	
JAVASCRIPT	
JQUERY	
ANGULAR 1.x	
ANGULAR 2.x	
Mobile Technologies:	
IONIC 3	
Server Technologies:	
MVC.NET	
C#	
JAVA	
Designing tools:	
PENCIL	
PHOTOSHOP	

MURALI KRISHNA SAI CHUKKA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE-

2017 - 2018

BUSINESS TECHNICAL ANALYST - DELOITTE

Responsibilities include Development, Unit testing, defect analysis, defect fixing, client interaction for clarification, maintaining the code quality and standards.

2014 - 2017 (

SOFTWARE ENGINEER - HCL

Joined as a campus hire and finished training on Microsoft technologies. Worked as a full stack developer.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2020

MASTER'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - PURSUING

UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI KANSAS CITY - USASpecialization in Web Development and Data Science.

2009 - 2013 (

BACHELOR'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - 77.45 %

VELAGAPUDI RAMAKRISHNA SIDDHARTHA ENGINEERING COLLEGE - INDIA Specialization in Web Development, Data Structures, Software engineering development models.

PROJECTS-

2018

FACTORY MAINTENANCE SYSTEM - UMKC

- Implemented mobile application using ionic 3.
- Increased the performance of UI by storing static data like images, js files etc., on client-side database.
- Implemented Excel import functionality.

2017 - 2018

TECO ENERGY - DELOITTE

- Convert globalization functionality from resource files to database. Provided user interface in admin portal for translation.
- Design user interfaces for Agent portal.

2016 - 2017

PANASONIC MMS - HCL

- Redesigned entire application (74 web pages) using Bootstrap within a month.
- Implemented schedule back up of the database via web application.
- Increase the performance of the dashboard data by converting server-side code to stored procedures.

2015 - 2016

PANASONIC WIP - HCL

- Setup base for the application using bootstrap and angularis.
- Implemented dashboards using jsPlumb library.
- Implemented charts functionality in the application.

2014 - 2015

MEDTRONIC - HCL

- Implemented a generic crud framework using bootstrap.
- Implemented import functionality.